bbfc.co.uk 2019-12-14

# Privacy statement | British Board of Film Classification

## Privacy Policy 

This privacy policy sets out how the BBFC uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website. 

The BBFC is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

The BBFC may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. 

### The information we collect and how we use it 

When someone visits our websites (bbfc.co.uk and cbbfc.co.uk) we use a third party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make, and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website. If we do want to collect personally identifiable information through our website, we will be clear about this. We will state when we collect personal information and will explain what we intend to do with it. 

We may collect personal information that you provide via forms on this website. 

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: 

  * To help us improve the services we provide 
  * To customise the website according to your interests 
  * To contact you for market research purposes

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. 

### Subscribing to newsletters

We use a third party supplier, MailChimp, to distribute our newsletters. If you subscribe to our newsletters you may click the unsubscribe link in our newsletter at any time. We clean our newsletter subscriber list annually to remove any subscribers not opening our newsletters. If you do interact with our newsletters we will continue to send them to you for up to 5 years, unless you unsubscribe.

### Requesting our student poster

If you request a copy of our student poster we will only retain your data for the purpose of sending the poster to you, after which your data will be destroyed.

### Requesting your data

If you have provided us with personal information over this website, and you wish to have your data removed from our records, please write to us at our offices, addressing your letter to HR department, BBFC, 3 Soho Square, London, England, W1D 3HD, or [email us](mailto:feedback@bbfc.co.uk).

If we do hold information about you we will:

• give you a description of it;  
• tell you why we are holding it;  
• tell you who it could be disclosed to; and  
• let you have a copy of the information in an intelligible form.

### How we use cookies 

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie analyses your activity on a website. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages users are visiting on this website. This helps us to analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to our customers' needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. 

### Other websites 

This policy only addresses our activities from our servers. Other websites (including those that we link to) may have their own policies, which we do not control, and thus are not addressed by this policy. 

### Disclaimer 

The BBFC makes no warranties in respect of the content on its site. It assumes no responsibility for the accuracy or reliability of any of the content on this site. The content is only for your general information and use and is provided on an 'as is' and 'as available' basis. 

The information provided on this website may be out of date, and may be changed or updated without notice. The BBFC does not accept any liability for any error, omission or failure to update such information. 

The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. Whilst we endeavour to keep the information up-to-date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk. 

In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website. 

Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under the control of the BBFC. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them. 

Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, the BBFC takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.
